# Minyoung Kim

mymykim511@gmail.com | 9293105596 https://www.linkedin.com/in/minyoung-kim-822712137 408 E 92nd St. NEW YORK, NY 10128

#### **SUMMARY**

Successful at creating and improving designs to meet company brand styles and business needs. Prepared to offer 1+ years of development experience to a growing company. 3+ years of experience developing applications with HTML/CSS/JS and React.js. I am a fast learner who is very good at teamwork and likes to work with people who want to build a brand in a strategic way.

#### **SKILLS**

• React.js

JavaScript

MySQL

Node.js

CSS

Java

HTML

Python

Photoshop

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Front-end Developer

MTY Group | https://koriny.com | New York, NY | Aug 2021-Current

- Maintained, developed, and designed the website with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js
- Web Design and analyzing and fixing UI bugs
- Website was renewed in cooperation with UI/UX designers.
- Experience with REST/JSON APIs
- Developing the Web Application in an AWS
- Experience using MySQL
- Collaborating with UX designers and Back End Developers

## Web Developer/Website Manager

Ginza Man, DAS Outfitters | Suwanee, Georgia | Oct 2017-Apr 2018

- Make Online Shop and Management with Shopify
- Editing and Uploading of Image
- Maintained and designed the website

#### **General Manager**

Vintage Hollywood | Seoul, South Korea, South Korea | Mar 2010-Jul 2011

- Homepage & Product Management
- Created and Designed Documents
- Customer Service

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**Bachelor of Science**: Computer Science

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA | January 2021

- Major in Computer Science
- Threads: Media & Information Internetworks
- Junior Design Project 1st prize, 2019

**Associate of Arts:** Business

Ansan University | | Ansan, South Korea | February 2010

• Major in Internet Commerce